amourvert.com 2019-01-11

# Privacy Policy – Amour Vert

### **Amour Vert Privacy Policy**

Last Updated May 24th, 2018

Welcome to the web site (the “Site”) of Amour Vert, Inc. (“Amour Vert”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”). This Site is operated by Amour Vert and has been created to provide information about our company and its creative collaboration services   (the “Services”) to our users (“you”, “your”). This Privacy Policy sets forth Amour Vert’s policy with respect to information including personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”) and other information that is collected from Site visitors and users of the Services.

### **Personal Information We Collect**

We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information such as when you register for access to the Services, use certain Services, contact us with inquiries or respond to one of our surveys. Wherever Amour Vert collects Personal Data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy.

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Amour Vert and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States.

Non-Identifiable or Aggregated Data: When you interact with Amour Vert through the Site or Services, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Amour Vert may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Amour Vert affiliates, agents or service providers. This Site may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers, and how our users use and interact with the Amour Vert Service.  Also, in an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, Amour Vert often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis. Amour Vert may share this non-identifiable and aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners, but this type of non-identifiable and aggregate information does not identify you personally. Amour Vert may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

   \- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

   \- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

   \- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, PayPal or Apple Pay information), email address, and phone number.  We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

We may also collect offline data, data of your purchases in our stores as well as third-party lists for direct mail.

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

### **How We Use Your Information**

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).  Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

Communicate with you;

Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and

When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

### **Sharing Your Personal Information**

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.  For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Amour Vert is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

            Business Transfers: As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. 

            Related Companies: We may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

            Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties: Amour Vert, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.         

            Legal Requirements: Amour Vert may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Amour Vert, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

### **Behavioural Advertising**

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

   FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads

   GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  http://optout.aboutads.info/.

### **Do Not Track**

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

### **European Resident Rights**

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

### **Data Retention**

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

### **Children**

Amour Vert does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Site. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data on this Site without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to Amour Vert through this Site, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

### **Links to Other Web Sites**

### This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site. This Site may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by Amour Vert (the “Third Party Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from this Site do not imply that Amour Vert endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

### **Integrating Third Party Services within the Service**

One of the special features of the Service is that it allows you to enable various online third party services, such as social media and networking services, (“Third Party Services”) to be directly integrated into your Amour Vert experience. By directly integrating these services, we make your online experiences richer, and more personalized. To take advantage of this feature, we will ask you to provide us your username and password for the relevant Third Party Services. By enabling such Third Party Services, you are allowing us to pass your log-in information to these service providers for this purpose. When you add a Third Party Service account to the Service, we will collect your login information and other relevant information necessary to enable the Service to access that Third Party Service and your data contained within that Third Party Service.  However, please remember that the manner in which Third Party Services use, store and disclose your information is governed solely by the policies of such third parties, and Amour Vert shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Third Party Service that may be enabled within the Service.

### **Security**

Amour Vert takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Site from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet, email or other electronic transmission is ever fully secure or error free, so you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us in this way.

### **Other Terms and Conditions**

Your access to and use of this Site is subject to the Terms of Service.

### **Changes to Amour Vert’s Privacy Policy**

The Site and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for Amour Vert to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Amour Vert reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Site after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

### **Contacting Amour Vert**

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@amourvert.com or by mail using the details provided below:

1278 Minnesota St, San Francisco CA, CA, 94107, United States
